They
try
to break the circle They try to tear the seam But
you can't put a price tag on the architects of a
dream
We stood out in the freezing rain Our backs
against the wall But looking at the five of us, I
knew we'd never fall
The compass always points me back to you The only
thing I've ever known is true
We built a fortress out of the fire We took the
engine and we pushed it higher Through the
static and the heavy weather We proved that
family always sticks together Oh, we're
standing in the light Yeah, we won the fight
tonight
We didn't need the spotlight, didn't need the
gold We kept the only promises that never could
be sold From the dorm rooms in the valley to the
neon city streets
The rhythm of this family Is the only heart that
beats The compass always points me back to you
The only thing I've ever known is true We built a
fortress out of the fire We took the engine and we
pushed it higher Through the static and the
heavy weather We proved that family always
sticks together Oh, we're standing in the
light. Yeah, we won the fight tonight. Shh. Shh.
Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh.
Shh.
Oh.
No more shadows No more running blind We're
leaving all the empty noise
behind
We built a fortress out of the fire. We took the
engine and we pushed it higher. Through the
static and the heavy weather, we proved that
family always sticks together. Oh, we're
standing in the light. Yeah, we won the fight
tonight. Standing in the light.
Family sticks together